<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Artificial Intelligence on wlsc</title><link>https://wlsc.de/categories/artificial-intelligence/</link><description>Recent content in Artificial Intelligence on wlsc</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wlsc.de/categories/artificial-intelligence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Apple releases its first AI paper</title><link>https://wlsc.de/posts/2017-01-01-apple-releases-its-first-ai-paper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wlsc.de/posts/2017-01-01-apple-releases-its-first-ai-paper/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="learning-from-simulated-and-unsupervised-images-through-adversarial-training"&gt;
 Learning from Simulated and Unsupervised Images through Adversarial Training
 &lt;a class="heading-link" href="#learning-from-simulated-and-unsupervised-images-through-adversarial-training"&gt;
 &lt;i class="fa-solid fa-link" aria-hidden="true" title="Link to heading"&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
 &lt;span class="sr-only"&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://wlsc.de/images/2017/01/apple_first_paper.jpg" &gt;&lt;img src="https://wlsc.de/images/2017/01/apple_first_paper-1024x560.jpg" alt="Apple first AI paper"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first paper from Apple company regarding Artificial Intelligence with Deep
Learning &lt;a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/1612.07828" class="external-link" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;is published&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Bay Area Deep Learning School lectures (Stanford)</title><link>https://wlsc.de/posts/2016-09-25-bay-area-deep-learning-school-lectures-stanford/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wlsc.de/posts/2016-09-25-bay-area-deep-learning-school-lectures-stanford/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The Deep Learning School is a great two day set of introduction lectures on Machine Learning, Natural Language
Processing and Computer Vision for Deep Learning. The two days event is solely dedicated to Deep Learning! The lectures
take place at CEMEX auditorium at the Graduate School of Business on Stanford campus (CA, USA) and include a variety of
prominent speakers from the above mentioned research fields.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Deepmind AI reduces Google data center cooling bill by 40%</title><link>https://wlsc.de/posts/2016-07-22-deepmind-ai-reduces-google-data-center-cooling-bill-by-40/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wlsc.de/posts/2016-07-22-deepmind-ai-reduces-google-data-center-cooling-bill-by-40/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;From smartphone assistants to image recognition and translation, machine learning already helps us in our everyday
lives. But it can also help us to tackle some of the world’s most challenging physical problems — such as energy
consumption. Large-scale commercial and industrial systems like data centres consume a lot of energy, and while much has
been done to stem the growth of energy use, there remains a lot more to do given the world’s increasing need for
computing power.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reducing energy usage has been a major focus for us over the past 10 years: we have built our own super-efficient
servers at Google, invented more efficient ways to cool our data centres and invested heavily in green energy sources,
with the goal of being powered 100 percent by renewable energy. Compared to five years ago, we now get around 3.5 times
the computing power out of the same amount of energy, and we continue to make many improvements each year.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Concrete AI safety problems</title><link>https://wlsc.de/posts/2016-06-22-concrete-ai-safety-problems/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wlsc.de/posts/2016-06-22-concrete-ai-safety-problems/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Concrete AI safety problems&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; paper by &lt;em&gt;Dario Amodei (Google Brain), Chris Olah (Google Brain), Jacob
Steinhardt (Stanford University), Paul Christiano (UC Berkeley), John Schulman (OpenAI), Dan Mané (Google Brain)&lt;/em&gt;
suggests a new approach to the Machine Learning (ML) and Artificial Intelligence (AI) research, which focuses more on
productivity of forward-looking applications while building cutting-edge AI systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A number of key problems considered in the paper as well as their descriptions are listed below. In the paper authors
also elaborate on how to approach each of the given problem.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>